Eugh.
Argh.
Ah...
Whzens slugs, a geez.
Winds ...
Huuuugh.
Huffs What?
Nice.
I'll see you next time.
How is this possible?
I know I chopped her leg off, but it's piercing my back now.
She regenerated it already.
No way.
If that's true, that would make your regenerative powers greater than my own.
I'll see you next time.
She'll never be the same.
Get off me, you damn brat!
I'll chop you into pieces and stuff you into my belt!
She stopped it with her severed limbs?
No.
Her coagulated blood is keeping them connected.
Her blood is burning me!
Just like that day!
Fire!
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
No, don't. You have to stop it.
Listen to me. You can pull through this.
Please forgive me. It's my fault you had to fight.
This whole area reeks of Nezuko's blood now.
I can tell just how badly she was wounded during the time I was passed out.
It hurt you, didn't it? I know you suffered. I'm sorry, but it's all right now. I promise I won't let anyone hurt you ever again.
You've got to go to sleep, Nezuko. Go to sleep so you can heal yourself.
Nezuko!
Please.
What's going on?
I don't know. They just burst through the floors.
Zu... come. Just sleep.
You've got some nerve doing that to me.
So, you can use blood demon art as well.
I've never heard of a blood demon art that only burns demons.
Whatever you did is taking me forever to heal from.
You're starting to irritate me like no other.
I'm through playing around.
This is bad.
There are people here that I have to protect.
I have to think and take action.
Her attack will come any second now, which will shred this whole building.
I can't just let go of Nezuko.
But if I don't, these people will get hurt.
Hey.
So, is this Nezuko Kamado?
Quite the flashy way to demonize.
When did you get here?
All that fancy talk in front of the Master?
And you let her wreak havoc like this?
No one said she could demonize so flashily!
Thanks for coming.
You're a Hashira, right?
I've been here waiting for you.
Shut up.
I'm not here to waste my time on you.
Get lost.
After all, you're no upper-ranked demon.
Not when you're that weak.
You're not the one I've been searching for.
So beat it.
Come again?
How dare you speak to...
Huh?
Damn it!
How did we lose sight of the God of Festivals already?
At this rate, we'll be locked in the dark!
In a flashy way, of course.
Hey, you spotted him?
I hope you're ready, worm lady!
Cause the mountain god lordy knows how you're coming through!
Wait...
What?
She's beheaded!
But how?
Was it Mr. Uzui who did that?
He's unreal!
Hey!
The battle here is far from over.
So get her under control.
Yes, I'll go!
Brats who throw temper tantrums don't belong on the battlefield.
Can't you sing her a lullaby or something?
It's no use.
My voice isn't reaching her.
She's not listening to me at all.
Mother...
What do I do?
Can't you sing her a lullaby or something?
Hush, hush, baby rabbit!
Up there on the hill!
Why are your...
Ears so very long!
When I was small!
Mother!
Eat...
The leaves...
Of a tall tree!
And that's why...
My...
Ears...
Are so long!
Nesuko?
Hush, baby rabbit!
Baby rabbit!
Up there on the hill!
Why is it your eyes are so red, my little rabbit?
You see, before I was ever born, my mother decided one day to eat the red fruit of the tree.
So little bunny that I might be, my eyes are red from that tree.
I think I'm starting to get what happened now.
So the reason brother's eyes are red, is because you ate red berries when he was inside your tummy.
Nesuko?
It worked.
You hear that, Mother?
That mother, it worked. She's sound asleep.
Mr. Uzui...
Where do you think you're going? Get back here, you brute!
You have the gall to behead me and walk away? You're going to pay for this!
Would you just shut up already? You've been nothing but unflashy, so drop dead.
Don't give me that crap! I'm stronger than you! So what makes you think that I'm not an upper rank?
Sorry, but you can't be an upper rank.
I will have you know that I am upper six!
Then why are you holding your severed head right now? I mean, come on.
What, did I cut your brains out too?
Just because I'm like this doesn't mean I've lost yet! I'm an upper rank, dammit!
I think it's pretty obvious that you lost.
I'm just more powerful than you can comprehend! I might be number six right now, but I'm going to get even stronger!
Don't care, didn't ask.
I really have an upper six! I really have an upper six! I've even got the number to prove it too!
You just can't accept how amazing I am!
You're kidding. She's throwing a tantrum?
Wait a second. How is she able to talk for this long?
Even though she was beheaded, her body hasn't disintegrated.
Die! Die! Die! All of you can just die!
He cut my head off! He cut my head off!
Help me, brother!
Come on now. There's no use crying about it, you know?
Can't you even manage to reattach your own head by yourself?
Well, you haven't always been the sharpest tool in the shed, have you?
She's still alive even after I beheaded her.
More importantly, who's that guy with her?
His reflexes are unreal.
Oh, is that a burn on your face?
You need to learn how to take better care of your face, you know?
After all, you were born with such a pretty face compared to mine.
Oh, not bad. I was going in for the kill, you know.
But you were able to stop me, weren't you?
Good for you.
Really.
You're a lucky guy, aren't you?
That face of yours.
Nice. I like your skin, too.
Not a blemish birthmark or scar to be seen anywhere, huh?
And you've got some meat on your bones.
I can't gain weight no matter what, see?
And you're tall as well.
You look like you're well over six feet, aren't you?
I guess you must get tons of attention from the ladies, don't you?
I envy you.
Oh, I envy you.
Would you mind just dropping dead and in the most agonizing way at the end?
Like getting skinned alive or maybe even getting that belly of yours lit open?
And one more thing, you oversized meat sack.
Brother, wait.
He's not the only one who was arresting me.
Kill the ones who burned me, too.
Kill them.
I've been toiling away over here and yet...
Even though I've given it my all, they won't die!
I feel like they tried everything, but they kept getting back up and picking on me!
They kicked up and bullied me, and I can't take it anymore!
I think I understand what's happening now, and what you did to her was unforgivable!
My sweet little sister was doing her best with what little brain she had to work with, and you bullied her!
I'll have to massacre everyone who laid a finger on her.
You could say I'm a firm believer in vengeance.
So I'll exact the same pain you inflicted upon her.
When you die, those words will ring through your skull.
I'll show no mercy, because my name is Gyataro!
What are those?
Sickles?
They're heading back towards Mr. Uzui.
Something's not right.
The belt demon never used a sickle.
Is it a new demon?
I smell Mr. Uzui's blood.
I've gotta back him up!
Where are you, worm belt?
Lord Inosuke has arrived!
You can run, but you can't hide!
Inosuke, Zenitsu...
Zenitsu, are you asleep?
You two, go and help Mr. Uzui.
Hurry!
Sit back, relax, and leave it to me!
I'm ready to go for a snack!
Yours truly, Lord Inosuke will handle it!
Hey, flash in me!
Thanks.
I'll put Nezuko back in her box.
It should only take a second!
I will allow it!
Thank you!
I'm so envious I could die.
You really are a good-looking guy, aren't you?
Damn!
Protecting those humans?
Showing off like that?
I envy you.
In their eyes, you're some kind of brave hero, aren't you?
I bet their affection and gratitude towards you is immeasurable, you know?
Well, yeah.
I'm a flashy, glamorous ladies' man, so that's a no-brainer.
Not to brag, but I have three wives to boot.
Am I going deaf, or did you just say that you have three wives?
You've gotta be kidding me!
That's unforgivable!
Blood demon art!
Flying blood sickle!
These splashes of blood are like blades.
It's so many of them!
I have to protect the people.
What now?
An explosion?
So you're on the first floor now.
Run!
Quickly!
Like I've let you escape that easily.
Bend for me, flying blood sickles.
He can control each of the slashes.
Which means he'll keep moving them until they hit their target.
The sister didn't die even when she was decapitated.
That's unheard of.
Since these two are siblings,
can I get rid of them both if I behead the brother instead?
Is he the main unit?
One way to find out.
From what I can hear,
all the people upstairs have fled.
Look out!
The thing about us is we fight together and two is better than one, you know?
All that's like,
I'm equal to five,
All that's epic.
Everything about us is better than one, you know?
Obviously we are impossible to arrive, but for us are better than one of our viewers.
Just like,
all the people Cryptibal come in the forest.
Here are theseega典s
Thank you.
繰り返し 繰り返し 血を流す魂が 夢を見るその先に 輝いて輝いて 新しい朝が来る 希望がたまびく Oh yeah
キミオヨンデイルエネ
キミオヨンデイルエネラゾン
クルトラベルエネッ バシ people
キミオヨンデイルエネ空
キミオス 포 하니까
キミオヨンデイルエネ キミオヨンデイルエネ
キミオヨンニ深い
トインデイルエネルエネ エネロゼン
キミオヨ デイルエネッチ
out now and move forward even stronger. She'd say, let's all keep smiling.
Next, episode eight, gathering. Nezuko really is the best, huh?